[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are the three Benelux countries?", "correct_answer": "Belgium, Netherlands and Luxembourg", "incorrect_answers": ["Finland, Sweden and Denmark", "The U.S.A., Canada and Mexico", "Honduras, Nicaragua and Belize"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ross Rebagliati, Karine Ruby, Gian Simmen, Nicola Thost, Anton Pogue, Stacia Hookman, Steve Persons, and Sabrina Sadeghi are prominent names in this  sport.", "correct_answer": "Snowboarding", "incorrect_answers": ["Skiing", "Figure skating", "Team handball"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Donald Trump wore a solid pink tie in every episode of The Apprentice.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Is the tiger the largest cat out of the Big Cat group?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Kojiki and the Nihon Shoki are the sacred texts of which religion?", "correct_answer": "Shinto", "incorrect_answers": ["Taoism", "Sikhism", "Zoroastrianism"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what country is the popular tomato festival called La Tomatina celebrated annually?", "correct_answer": "Spain", "incorrect_answers": ["Chile", "Mexico", "Ecuador"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What feature would Pluto develop if placed as near to the Sun as Earth is?", "correct_answer": "A comet tail", "incorrect_answers": ["A highly elliptic orbit", "None of these", "A halo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Krahule hill , known as the geographic center of Europe, is it located in this country.", "correct_answer": "Slovakia", "incorrect_answers": ["Austria", "Montenegro", "Slovenia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Wes Anderson has many actors that appear quite often in his films. Can you name the college friend of Wes Andersons that appeared in The Darjeeling Limited and co-wrote Rushmore with Anderson?", "correct_answer": "Owen Wilson", "incorrect_answers": ["Ben Stiller", "Bill Murray", "Luke Wilson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What do these  people have in common: both Presidents Bush, actor James Spader, actor Jack Lemmon, actor Humphrey Bogart and writer Edgar Rice  Burroughs?", "correct_answer": "They all went to the same high school.", "incorrect_answers": ["They all were in Texas on 9/11/2001.", "They are the same Zodiac sign.", "They were all born in the same month."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Potassium iodide, sodium iodide, or sodium iodate are added to table salt in order to prevent iodine deficiency. What health problems does iodine deficiency cause?", "correct_answer": "Thyroid gland disorders", "incorrect_answers": ["Skin and bone disorders", "Adrenal gland malfunction", "Cardiovascular problems"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What city boasts the most parks in the US?", "correct_answer": "Denver, Colorado", "incorrect_answers": ["Colorado Springs, Colorado", "Golden, Colorado", "Aspen, Colorado"]}]